homewithgod.com 2011-10-06

# Christian Search Engine - Privacy Statement

### Privacy Statement

HomewithGod.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: HomewithGod.com.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We use cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

This site contains links to other sites. HomewithGod.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

#### Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

#### Children's Guidelines

HomewithGod.com Web site meets the guidelines of TRUSTe's Children's program.

**WE DO NOT** collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent.

**WE DO NOT** collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent.

**WE DO NOT** distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with out prior parental consent.

**WE DO NOT** give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent.

**WE DO NOT** entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity

#### Cookies

A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. HomewithGod.com uses cookies in only two instances--when you register as for HomewithGod.com free email and when you click an ad.

**Registration:** when you register, HomewithGod.com uses a cookie to store a unique, random user ID. We do not store passwords or any personal information about you. We use this ID to identify you anonymously in our database and to track the pages you visit on our site. Cookies also enable you to enter HomewithGod.com sites as a member without having to log on each time, and to visit member-restricted areas of the sites. We encrypt the user ID for added security.

**Ads:** HomewithGod.com's advertising system delivers a one-time cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates.

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use any HomewithGod.com site.

#### IP Address Practices Examples

The HomewithGod.com Web site also logs IP addresses for systems administration purposes. IP addresses are logged to track a user's session. This gives HomewithGod.com an idea of which parts of our site users are visiting. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a users session will be tracked, but the user will be anonymous.

#### Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

You can send email to [webmaster@homewithgod.com](mailto:webmaster@homewithgod.com)

#### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact:

HomewithGod Christian Resources  
899 RS CR 1690  
Lone Oak, TX 75453
